Jester Hairston Collection MS040
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Sound recordings unrelated to Jester Hairston, 1910 -- 1989; 1920 -- 1950; MS040.002; 25.2 Linear Feet; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Cannonball Adderley Quintet in San Francisco, 1959; MS040.002.018.00002; Cannonball Adderley Quintet (Box 18)
  - Capital University men's glee club, 1973; MS040.002.018.00003; Capitol University Men's Glee Club (Box 18)
  - Carolina lowcountry patois, 1950; MS040.002.018.00004; Reeves, Dick (Box 18)
  - Catch the choral spirit, 1982; MS040.002.018.00005; Jenson Publications (Box 18)
  - Cathedral choir at worship, 1970; MS040.002.018.00006; First Presbyterian Church of Hollywood (Box 18)
  - Choral capers, 1966; MS040.002.018.00007; Foothill College Choir (Box 18)
    1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./
  - Choral celebration, vol XI, 1981; MS040.002.018.00008; Jenson Publications (Box 18)
  - Choral celebration, vol XI, 1981; MS040.002.018.00009; Jenson Publications (Box 18)
  - Choral Christmas, 1971; MS040.002.018.00010; Treble Choir (Box 18)
  - Choral ensemble, 1984; MS040.002.018.00011; Jenson Publications (Box 18)
    0 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ There is no record accompanying this record jacket./
  - Christmas, 1969; MS040.002.018.00012; United States Air Force Band (Box 18)
  - The Christmas album, 1973; MS040.002.018.00013; Henry Sibley High School Choirs (Box 18)
  - A Christmas concert, 1968; MS040.002.018.00014; A Cappella Choir of Montebello (Box 18)
  - A Christmas concert, 1968; MS040.002.018.00015; A Cappella Choir of Montebello (Box 18)
  - A Christmas festival of song, 1981; MS040.002.018.00016; Sanctuary Choirs (Box 18)
  - A Christmas festival of song, 1981; MS040.002.018.00017; Sanctuary Choirs (Box 18)
  - A Christmas festival of song, 1981; MS040.002.018.00018; Sanctuary Choirs (Box 18)
  - A Christmas festival of song, 1981; MS040.002.018.00019; Sanctuary Choirs (Box 18)
  - Christmas in hymns and carols, 1965; MS040.002.018.00020; Sanctuary Choirs (Box 18)
  - Christmas in hymns and carols, volume 2, 1965; MS040.002.018.00021; Sanctuary Choirs (Box 18)
  - Christmas in song, 1972; MS040.002.018.00022; Southwest High School Choir (Box 18)
  - Christmas in stereo, 1968; MS040.002.018.00023; Chancel Choir (Box 18)
    The date is approximate./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Christmas voices of Walter Schumann, 1972; MS040.002.018.00024; Schumann, Walter (Box 18)
  - Christmas voices of Walter Schumann, 1972; MS040.002.018.00025; Schumann, Walter (Box 18)
  - Christmas with Placido Domingo, 1981; MS040.002.018.00026; Domingo, Placido (Box 18)
    1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket and descriptive booklet included./
  - Christmas with Placido Domingo, 1981; MS040.002.018.00027; Domingo, Placido (Box 18)
  - Christmas with the Tweed Family Singers, 1972; MS040.002.018.00028; Tweed Family Singers (Box 18)
  - Cielito lindo, 1973; MS040.002.018.00029; Mormon Tabernacle Choir (Box 18)
  - Come out swingin', 1975; MS040.002.018.00030; Airmen of Note (Box 18)
  - Comin' home, 1973; MS040.002.018.00031; Waldowski, Toby and Barb (Box 18)
  - Concert modern, 1958; MS040.002.018.00032; Les Brown and his Band of Renown (Box 18)
  - Coral salesmen's sampler #1, 1962; MS040.002.018.00033; Coral Records Inc. (Box 18)
  - Crafty hands, 1982; MS040.002.018.00034; Crafty Hands (Box 18)
  - The creation, 1952; MS040.002.018.00035; Lewis and Clark College Choir (Box 18)
  - Creation, 1955; MS040.002.018.00036; Prince Modupe (Box 18)
  - Deep river, 1958; MS040.002.018.00037; McFerrin, Robert (Box 18)
  - Deep river: an interpretation of five Negro spirituals, 1967; MS040.002.018.00038; Howard University Choir (Box 18)
  - Dream along with me, 1957; MS040.002.018.00039; Como, Perry (Box 18)
  - Duke Ellington and his famous orchestra and soloists, 1957; MS040.002.018.00040; Ellington, Duke (Box 18)
    This dates is approximate./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Duke Ellington and his famous orchestra and soloists, 1957; MS040.002.018.00041; Ellington, Duke (Box 18)
  - Duke Ellington and the Buck Clayton All-Stars ar Newport, 1956; MS040.002.018.00042; Ellington, Duke (Box 18)
  - Easin' it, 1960; MS040.002.019.00001; Count Basie and his orchestra (Box 19)
  - The easy winners, 1975; MS040.002.019.00002; Perlman, Itzhak (Box 19)
  - Echoes from a 16th century cathedral, 1967; MS040.002.019.00003; Roger Wagner Chorale (Box 19)
    This dates is approximate./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket and sleeve included./
  - Ecumenical choir recorded live in concert, 1978; MS040.002.019.00004; Ecumenical Choir (Box 19)
  - Edmond de Luca's safari, 1957; MS040.002.019.00005; The Trans-World Symphony Orchestra (Box 19)
  - Elijah, 1971; MS040.002.019.00006; Santa Clara Chorale (Box 19)
  - Elm School chorus (side one: do re mi), 1975; MS040.002.019.00007; Elm School Chorus (Box 19)
  - Elm School chorus (side one: Hawaii Ponoi), 1975; MS040.002.019.00008; Elm School Chorus (Box 19)
  - Elm School chorus (side one: the Star Spangled Banner), 1975; MS040.002.019.00009; Elm School Chorus (Box 19)
  - Elm School chorus (side one: Timber Trail), 1975; MS040.002.019.00010; Elm School Chorus (Box 19)
  - Europa cantat, 1969; MS040.002.019.00011; Sibley High School Choir (Box 19)
  - Father knows best, 1982; MS040.002.019.00012; Waldowski, Toby and Barb (Box 19)
  - Favorite overtures, 1978; MS040.002.019.00013; United States Air Force Band (Box 19)
  - Favorite overtures volume 2, 1979; MS040.002.019.00014; United States Air Force Band (Box 19)
  - Favorite overtures volume 2, 1979; MS040.002.019.00015; United States Air Force Band (Box 19)
  - First Baptist Church of Vacherie, LA, 1982; MS040.002.019.00016 (Box 19)
  - First international university choral festival, 1966; MS040.002.019.00017; Scott, Howard (Box 19)
  - The flip sides of Grady Nutt, 1970; MS040.002.019.00018; Nutt, Grady (Box 19)
  - Folk music of Liberia, 1955; MS040.002.019.00019; Okie, Packard L. (Box 19)
  - Folk song festival, 1978; MS040.002.019.00020; Anne Campbell Singers (Box 19)
  - Folk songs of Africa, 1963; MS040.002.019.00021; McLaughlin, Roberta (Box 19)
  - For Christmas this year, 1966; MS040.002.019.00022; Lettermen (Box 19)
  - Forth in thy name, 1972; MS040.002.019.00023; Chapel Choir of First Baptist Church of Dallas (Box 19)
  - Fred Waring and the Pennsylvanians in hi-fi, 1957; MS040.002.019.00024; Fred Waring and his Pennsylvanians (Box 19)
  - Fred Waring and the Pennsylvanians in hi-fi, 1957; MS040.002.019.00025; Fred Waring and his Pennsylvanians (Box 19)
  - A German requiem, 1956; MS040.002.019.00026; Choir of St. Hedwig's Cathedral (Box 19)
  - Glad sounds of Christmas!, 1978; MS040.002.019.00027; Litchfield Area Male Chorus (Box 19)
  - Glad sounds of Christmas!, 1978; MS040.002.019.00028; Litchfield Area Male Chorus (Box 19)
  - Glendale Presbytarian Church choir, 1954; MS040.002.019.00029; Glendale Presbyterian Church Choir (Box 19)
  - Gloria, 1981; MS040.002.019.00030; Pfeiffer College Concert Choir (Box 19)
  - The glory of Christmas, 1981; MS040.002.019.00031; Jani, Robert F. (Box 19)
  - Go blow your horn, 1957; MS040.002.019.00032; Louis Jordan and his Tympany Five (Box 19)
  - God bless America, 1965; MS040.002.019.00033; Mormon Tabernacle Choir (Box 19)
  - God bless Tiny Tim, 1968; MS040.002.019.00034; Tiny Tim (Box 19)
  - Good news, 1962; MS040.002.019.00035; Alex Sharpe Choral Ensemble (Box 19)
  - Granite Youth Symphony, 1972; MS040.002.019.00036 (Box 19)
  - Great German songs, 1965; MS040.002.020.00001; Hotter, Hans (Box 20)
    1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket and sleeve and descriptive booklet included./
  - Great songs of Christmas, album seven, 1967; MS040.002.020.00002; Bennett, Tony (Box 20)
  - Gullah, 1963; MS040.002.020.00003; Reeves, Dick (Box 20)
  - Hallelujah, 1973; MS040.002.020.00004; Tulsa Public Schools All-City Senior High School (Box 20)
  - Have yourself a soulful little Christmas, 1984; MS040.002.020.00005; Burrell, Kenny (Box 20)
    1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket and other additional material included./
  - He touched me, 1970; MS040.002.020.00006; Glover, Kenneth (Box 20)
  - A heritage in hymns, 1984; MS040.002.020.00007; Wesley, Charles (Box 20)
  - Hiawatha's wedding feast, 1984; MS040.002.020.00008; Boston Orchestra and Chorale (Box 20)
  - Hickory Holler revisited, 1968; MS040.002.020.00009; Smith, O.C. (Box 20)
  - His eye is on the sparrow, 1966; MS040.002.020.00010; Waters, Ethel (Box 20)
  - His eye is on the sparrow, 1966; MS040.002.020.00011; Waters, Ethel (Box 20)
    1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket for this record was replaced with record jacket of another record./
  - Holiday for strings, 1954; MS040.002.020.00012; Rose, David (Box 20)
  - How great thou art, 1980; MS040.002.020.00013; Singing Men of Southeast Texas (Box 20)
  - How sweet the sound, 1975; MS040.002.020.00014; Sanctuary Choir of First Baptist Church, Dallas, Texas (Box 20)
  - Hymns triumphant, 1981; MS040.002.020.00015; London Philharmonic Choir and National Philharmonic Orchestr (Box 20)
  - I know my love, 1961; MS040.002.020.00016; Terri, Salli (Box 20)
  - I know my love, 1961; MS040.002.020.00017; Terri, Salli (Box 20)
  - I never saw another butterfly, 1983; MS040.002.020.00018; San Francisco Girls Chorus (Box 20)
  - I'll keep singin', 1978; MS040.002.020.00019; Waldowski, Toby and Barb (Box 20)
  - The immortal Johnny Dodds, 1966; MS040.002.020.00020; Dodds, Johnny (Box 20)
  - I'm steppin' high!, 1975; MS040.002.020.00021; Hannah, Jack (Box 20)
  - In a tender mood, 1957; MS040.002.020.00022; Hodges, Johnny (Box 20)
  - In concert, 1966; MS040.002.020.00023; Yuba City High School Vocal Music Department (Box 20)
  - In our hearts you're number one, 1976; MS040.002.020.00024; Metropolitan Boys Choir (Box 20)
  - In Praise of Oxala and Other Gods: Black Music of South America, 1970; MS040.002.020.00025; Lewiston, David (Box 20)
  - In the heat of the night original motion picture soundtrack, 1967; MS040.002.020.00026; Jones, Quincy (Box 20)
  - In the night, 1962; MS040.002.020.00027; George Shearing Quintet (Box 20)
  - Israel in Egypt, 1965; MS040.002.020.00028; Foothill College Choir (Box 20)
  - Italian and reformation symphonies, 1965; MS040.002.020.00029; Toscanini, Arturo (Box 20)
  - I've made up my mind, 1973; MS040.002.020.00030; Hannah, Jack (Box 20)
  - Jazz kaleidoscope, 1955; MS040.002.020.00031; Brown, Pete (Box 20)
  - Jazz...rock...pop...gospel...blues...the works, 1980; MS040.002.020.00032; College of the Siskiyous Jazz Choir (Box 20)
  - The jazz story, volume 1, 1964; MS040.002.020.00033; Dexter, Dave (Box 20)
  - The jazz story, volume 2, 1964; MS040.002.020.00034; Dexter, Dave (Box 20)
  - The jazz story, volume 3, 1964; MS040.002.020.00035; Dexter, Dave (Box 20)
  - The jazz story, volume 4, 1964; MS040.002.020.00036; Dexter, Dave (Box 20)
  - The jazz story, volume 5, 1964; MS040.002.020.00037; Dexter, Dave (Box 20)
  - Jazz 1940 era, 1960; MS040.002.020.00038; Moore, Oscar (Box 20)
  - Jefferson a cappella choir, 1967; MS040.002.020.00039; Jefferson A Cappella Choir (Box 20)
  - Jesus, 1983; MS040.002.020.00040; Spurr, Thurlow (Box 20)
  - Jesus: the life of Jesus in twelve contemporary songs, 1969; MS040.002.020.00041; McCarthy, John (Box 20)
  - Jesus Christ superstar, 1970; MS040.002.020.00042; Webber, Andrew Lloyd (Box 20)
  - Jewish holiday songs, 1977; MS040.002.020.00043; Moshe Hillel (Box 20)
  - Johann Sebastian Bach, 1971; MS040.002.020.00044; Kassel Vocal Ensemble (Box 20)
  - A jubilant song, 1976; MS040.002.020.00045; Mormon Tabernacle Choir (Box 20)
  - Jubilant song, 1970; MS040.002.021.00001; Lewis and Clark College Choir (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Judas Maccabaeus, 1977; MS040.002.021.00002; Handel, G. F. (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
    3 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket and descriptive booklet included./
  - Just want to be loved, 1989; MS040.002.021.00003; Topaz (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - The king and I [original cast album], 1958; MS040.002.021.00004; Rodgers, Richard (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - King Kong, 1961; MS040.002.021.00005; Matshikiza, Todd (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - King of the savoy, volume two, 1963; MS040.002.021.00006; Webb, Chick (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - The lady from Philadelphia, 1958; MS040.002.021.00007; Anderson, Marian (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Latin American songs, a choral concert, 1949; MS040.002.021.00008; de Paur's Infantry Chorus (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Latvian folk songs, volume two, 1966; MS040.002.021.00009; Andreassen, Alden (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Lena Horne, 1957; MS040.002.021.00010; Horne, Lena (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Les chanson's nostalgiques, 1960; MS040.002.021.00011; Peyton, Roy (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Let us go into the house of the Lord, 1969; MS040.002.021.00012; The Edwin Hawkins Singers (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Lewis and Clark College choir, volume two, 1965; MS040.002.021.00013; Lewis and Clark College Choir (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - The life of Christ, 1963; MS040.002.021.00014; Hayes, Roland (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - The Life treasury of American folk music, 1961; MS040.002.021.00015; Bluestein, Gene (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Lift every voice, 1967; MS040.002.021.00016; Song Crafters (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - A Lincoln treasury, 1959; MS040.002.021.00017; Lyn Murray and His Orchestra (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Litchfield male chorus, 1968; MS040.002.021.00018; Litchfield Area Male Chorus (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Litchfield school chorus, 1970; MS040.002.021.00019; Litchfield School Chorus (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - "Live" at Carnegie Hall, 1973; MS040.002.021.00020; Andrae Crouch and the Disciples (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Lord, I need you, 1965; MS040.002.021.00021; Shebeck, Bev (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - The Lord is my light, 1981; MS040.002.021.00022; Talley, Dana and Sue (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - The Lord is my shepherd, 1958; MS040.002.021.00023; Mormon Tabernacle Choir (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Lord, listen to your children, 1970; MS040.002.021.00024; Sanctuary Choir of First Baptist Church, Dallas, Texas (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Lord teach me the way, 1960; MS040.002.021.00025; Taylor, Carl H. (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Lord teach me the way, 1960; MS040.002.021.00026; Taylor, Carl H. (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Los Cantadores in concert, 1967; MS040.002.021.00027; Los Cantadores (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Luau: the Hawaiian festival of true Hawaiian music, dances, excitement, and food, 1965; MS040.002.021.00028; Taylor, Carl H. (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Lunceford special, 1967; MS040.002.021.00029; Lunceford, Jimmie (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Luther College concert band, 1965; MS040.002.021.00030; Luther College (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Mad about the boy, 1958; MS040.002.021.00031; Previn, Andre (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Madama Butterfly, 1965; MS040.002.021.00032; Metropolitan Opera (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
    3 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket and descriptive booklet and additional materials included./
  - The Madrigal singers of Illinois State, 1974; MS040.002.021.00033; University Madrigal Singers (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Madrigal singers, 1965; MS040.002.022.00001; Berger, Hindemith, and Byrd (Box 22)
  - Madrigal singers, 1960; MS040.002.022.00002; Santa Barbara High School (Box 22)
  - Make up - to break up, 1960; MS040.002.022.00003; J.R. and James (Box 22)
    1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Descriptive booklet included./
  - Marches around the world, 1973; MS040.002.022.00004; Singing Sergeants (Box 22)
  - Marcus Hall, 1970; MS040.002.022.00005; Hall, Marcus (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Martha Schlamme sings Jewish folk songs, 1957; MS040.002.022.00006; Schlamme, Martha (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - The Mass, 1965; MS040.002.022.00007; Choir of the Church of Santa Susanna (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Masterwork editions and contemporary choral literature, vol vii, 1979; MS040.002.022.00008; Jenson Publications (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
    1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket and additional materials included./
  - Masterwork editions and contemporary choral literature, vol vii, 1979; MS040.002.022.00009; Jenson Publications (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Matinee!, 1970; MS040.002.022.00010; Singing Sergeants (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Matinee!, 1970; MS040.002.022.00011; Singing Sergeants (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - McMurry College Chanters, 1970; MS040.002.022.00012 (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Merry Christmas, 1979; MS040.002.022.00013; Mills Brothers (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Merry Christmas from George Kennedy, 1979; MS040.002.022.00014; Singing Sergeants (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Merry Christmas from the Young Americans, 1975; MS040.002.022.00015; Young Americans (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Messiah, 1984; MS040.002.022.00016; Handel, G. F. (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Messiah, 1969; MS040.002.022.00017; Handel, G. F. (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Messiah sing, 1972; MS040.002.022.00018; Schola Cantorum (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Methodist youth singers in concert, 1965; MS040.002.022.00019; Methodist Youth Singers (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Mexican folk songs, 1955; MS040.002.022.00020; Mejia, Miguel Aceves (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - The Millikin choir 1970, MS040.002.022.00021; Millikin University (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Missa Solemnis in D minor, 1961; MS040.002.022.00022; Oneonta Congregational Church (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Montage, 1981; MS040.002.022.00023; Patterson Twins (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Monteverdi, 1937; MS040.002.022.00024; Boulanger, Nadia (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Mormon Tabernacle Choir concert of sacred music, 1955; MS040.002.022.00025; Mormon Tabernacle Choir (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Moscow nights: popular russian hits, 1970; MS040.002.022.00026; Vechera, Podmoskovni (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Mozart: seven overtures, 1960; MS040.002.022.00027; National Gallery Orchestra (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Mozart: orgelsolo-messe, kv259, 1967; MS040.002.022.00028; Vienna Choir Boys (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Msingi workshop / the declaration, 1965; MS040.002.022.00029; Bolsa Grande Concert Choir (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Music conference concert: Music and the world, 1970; MS040.002.022.00030; Forest Home Christian Conference Center (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Music for chorus, 1982; MS040.002.022.00031; Ives, Charles (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Music for listening, 1965; MS040.002.022.00032; Voorhees, Donald (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Music for moderns, 1958; MS040.002.022.00033; Moore, Phil (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Music for the choral ensemble, 1982; MS040.002.022.00034; Jenson Publications (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
  - Music! music! for the choral ensemble, 1981; MS040.002.022.00035; Jenson Publications (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
    2 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket and mailing envelope included./
  - Music! music! for the choral ensemble, 1981; MS040.002.022.00036; Jenson Publications (Box data_value_missing_a3550e346250721516e2d8704cefdb14)
    2 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket, mailing envelope and additional materials included./
  - Music to remember, 1962; MS040.002.023.00001; Talley, Dana and Sue (Box 23)
  - Musical Americana, 1971; MS040.002.023.00002; United States Air Force Band (Box 23)
  - A musical sampler, 1975; MS040.002.023.00003; The John Biggs Consort (Box 23)
  - My eyes have seen..., 1973; MS040.002.023.00004; Odetta (Box 23)
  - My Lord what a mornin', 1960; MS040.002.023.00005; Belafonte, Harry (Box 23)
  - My tribute to God be the glory, 1965; MS040.002.023.00006; Hawker, John (Box 23)
    1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record sleeve included./
  - New day with the Certain Sounds, 1976; MS040.002.023.00007; The Certain Sounds (Box 23)
  - New horizons for jazz ensemble, 1980; MS040.002.023.00008; Jenson Publications (Box 23)
  - New music for choral ensemble: senior choir edition, 1984; MS040.002.023.00009; Jenson Publications (Box 23)
  - A new song, 1981; MS040.002.023.00010; Coral Ridge Chancel Choir (Box 23)
  - Now hear this, 1975; MS040.002.023.00011; Amen Choir (Box 23)
  - Oklahoma!, 1975; MS040.002.023.00012; Rodgers, Richard (Box 23)
  - On the Air, 1976; MS040.002.023.00013; The Airmen of Note (Box 23)
  - ...one nation under God, 1982; MS040.002.023.00014; Singing Sergeants (Box 23)
  - ...one nation under God, 1982; MS040.002.023.00015; Singing Sergeants (Box 23)
  - The orchestra, 1979; MS040.002.023.00016; Elliot, Jack (Box 23)
  - Organ psalms and hymn variations, 1965; MS040.002.023.00017; Obetz, John (Box 23)
  - Original songs, 1970; MS040.002.023.00018; Young, Dennis (Box 23)
  - Originals by the Medical Mission Sisters: in love, 1971; MS040.002.023.00019; Medical Mission Sisters (Box 23)
  - Pacific Lutheran University's choir of the west, 1970; MS040.002.023.00020; Pacific Lutheran University (Box 23)
  - Palestrina: Pope Marcellus mass, 1960; MS040.002.023.00021; Roger Wagner Chorale (Box 23)
  - Pastel moods, 1965; MS040.002.023.00022; Oscar Peterson Trio (Box 23)
  - Piano rags by Scott Joplin, 1970; MS040.002.023.00023; Rifkin, Joshua (Box 23)
  - Piano starts here, 1968; MS040.002.023.00024; Tatum, Art (Box 23)
  - Porgy and Bess, 1958; MS040.002.023.00025; Gershwin, George (Box 23)
  - Porgy and Bess, 1976; MS040.002.023.00026; Gershwin, George (Box 23)
  - The power and the glory, 1981; MS040.002.023.00027; Mormon Tabernacle Choir (Box 23)